Hussein Al-Sayed Hassan Abdullah

FULL STACK PHP DEVELOPER



01017285081

Gharbia - Cairo

in linkedin.com/in/hussain-al-sid-782770255

github.com/hussain521

SUMMARY

A Software Engineer || Full Stack Developer with Extensive Experience in Developing Web Applications using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, React JS, C++ and Problem Solving. Committed to Delivering High-Quality Work. I Did Some Projects with the college, My Self and Join Training With the National Telecommunications Institute NTI And Training With Information Technology Institute ITI

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Createivo

Full - Stack PHP July 2024 – present

National Telecommunication Institute NTI

The summer training program has 120 hours in two parts: Soft skills / Freelance skills part 30 hours. Technical part 90 hours. August 2024 – September 2024

Information Technology Institute ITI

The summer training program has 120 hours Full Stack PHP Laravel July 2024 – August 2024

IEEE Kafrelsheikh Student Branch

Front - End March 2023 - May 2024

REFERENCES

Are Available Upon Request

EDUCATION

Faculty of Computer & Information Sciences - Kafr El-Sheikh University September 2021 - present

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Java Script
- My Sql
- PHP
- C++
- React JS

SOFT SKILLS

- Communication
- Faster Typing
- Problem Solving
- Creativity

LANGUAGES

- Arabic
- English